In this video we will talk
about ICICI Lord General Insurance Company. The
market cap of the company is
6947 4 crores and the P Ratio is 39.5%. If we
talk about the positive points in the company, then the
company has reduced its debt
and the company is almost debt free and the
dividend payout of the company is 29.3% and if we
talk about the negative points, then in the last 3
years the promoter's holding has reduced by 3.89%
and in the share holding, the promoter's
holding is 48%, PFI's holding is
22.3%, DI's holding is
18.1%, government's holding is
0.10% and public's holding is 11
% and now if we talk about the chart of the company, then
according to this trend line, a
support of 1400 is being formed and if you
want to do swing trading at this time, then you
can buy by placing a stop loss below 88%. That's all
in this video. If you liked the information given in the video, then
like the video, share it and
subscribe to our channel.